[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 2, "question": "But is anybody in Washington really happy now?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "anybody", "in", "Washington", "really", "happy", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 3, "answer": "This process has been messy.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "process", "has", "been", "messy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 7, "question": "Will this make the economy even worse?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "this", "make", "the", "economy", "even", "worse", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 8, "answer": "This agreement cast a long- term shadow on our nation's reasonableness and our reliability.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "agreement", "cast", "a", "long-", "term", "shadow", "on", "our", "nation", "'s", "reasonableness", "and", "our", "reliability", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "Has Congress shot itself in the foot?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "Congress", "shot", "itself", "in", "the", "foot", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "The American people hold us and their low opinion of us, because we are failing to do what they think is our job, and by the way, they are right.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "American", "people", "hold", "us", "and", "their", "low", "opinion", "of", "us", ",", "because", "we", "are", "failing", "to", "do", "what", "they", "think", "is", "our", "job", ",", "and", "by", "the", "way", ",", "they", "are", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "DT", "RB", "NN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "EX", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "No one expected that and it was really not a dry eye in the House, right?", "question_tokens": ["No", "one", "expected", "that", "and", "it", "was", "really", "not", "a", "dry", "eye", "in", "the", "House", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "It was very emotional, and understandably so, because we really haven't seen much of her a little bit when her husband took off on the shuttle, but there she was.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "very", "emotional", ",", "and", "understandably", "so", ",", "because", "we", "really", "have", "n't", "seen", "much", "of", "her", "a", "little", "bit", "when", "her", "husband", "took", "off", "on", "the", "shuttle", ",", "but", "there", "she", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party"]}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "Who's come out of this badly?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "come", "out", "of", "this", "badly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "Probably the Tea Party supporters have come out of it pretty well because they did manage successfully to get this entire issue linked, reducing the national debt and raising the debt ceiling.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "the", "Tea", "Party", "supporters", "have", "come", "out", "of", "it", "pretty", "well", "because", "they", "did", "manage", "successfully", "to", "get", "this", "entire", "issue", "linked", ",", "reducing", "the", "national", "debt", "and", "raising", "the", "debt", "ceiling", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "And pretty much stabbed the speaker, John Boehner flat in the back, didn't they?", "question_tokens": ["And", "pretty", "much", "stabbed", "the", "speaker", ",", "John", "Boehner", "flat", "in", "the", "back", ",", "did", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "I think that's a pretty good way of putting it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "a", "pretty", "good", "way", "of", "putting", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Boehner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Nobody really seems to believe, Erin, that anything in this deal is actually going to stimulate the American economy and that in itself is incredibly serious, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Nobody", "really", "seems", "to", "believe", ",", "Erin", ",", "that", "anything", "in", "this", "deal", "is", "actually", "going", "to", "stimulate", "the", "American", "economy", "and", "that", "in", "itself", "is", "incredibly", "serious", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Yes, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Erin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "Very quickly, Erin, predictions for the markets tomorrow morning?", "question_tokens": ["Very", "quickly", ",", "Erin", ",", "predictions", "for", "the", "markets", "tomorrow", "morning", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "It's going to be a tough one.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "a", "tough", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Erin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "Could his position be in jeopardy?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "his", "position", "be", "in", "jeopardy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP$", "NN", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "LITZER: I don't think his position is in jeopardy.", "answer_tokens": ["LITZER", ":", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "his", "position", "is", "in", "jeopardy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Where did you win and where did you lose in this debate?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "did", "you", "win", "and", "where", "did", "you", "lose", "in", "this", "debate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Well, I think the American people won in that we were able to bring down the deficit in this first step.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "American", "people", "won", "in", "that", "we", "were", "able", "to", "bring", "down", "the", "deficit", "in", "this", "first", "step", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "What did you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Well, it was extraordinary.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "extraordinary", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "-NONE-", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "Senator Sessions, how will you be voting tomorrow?", "question_tokens": ["Senator", "Sessions", ",", "how", "will", "you", "be", "voting", "tomorrow", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "I have decided I will not vote for the bill, although I really respect the people who've worked on it and the fact that it does take some real progress toward reducing spending, although far less than we need.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "decided", "I", "will", "not", "vote", "for", "the", "bill", ",", "although", "I", "really", "respect", "the", "people", "who", "'ve", "worked", "on", "it", "and", "the", "fact", "that", "it", "does", "take", "some", "real", "progress", "toward", "reducing", "spending", ",", "although", "far", "less", "than", "we", "need", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "What do you say of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "No, I know -- I think the Tea Party movement represented a spontaneous American expression of shock and concern over the spending that was going on in Washington.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "know", "--", "I", "think", "the", "Tea", "Party", "movement", "represented", "a", "spontaneous", "American", "expression", "of", "shock", "and", "concern", "over", "the", "spending", "that", "was", "going", "on", "in", "Washington", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "As a Republican, are you concerned about that or do you embrace it?", "question_tokens": ["As", "a", "Republican", ",", "are", "you", "concerned", "about", "that", "or", "do", "you", "embrace", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "I embrace it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "embrace", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "I mean it was tear-jerking, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "it", "was", "tear-jerking", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "It really was.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "really", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Can she have normal conversation?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "she", "have", "normal", "conversation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "UPTA: Well, you know what, when you think about, you know, cognition overall, Piers, it's sort of two ways to divide it.", "answer_tokens": ["UPTA", ":", "Well", ",", "you", "know", "what", ",", "when", "you", "think", "about", ",", "you", "know", ",", "cognition", "overall", ",", "Piers", ",", "it", "'s", "sort", "of", "two", "ways", "to", "divide", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "And from a therapeutic point of view, Sanjay, would something like today with the outpouring of emotion and everything else, would that be seen as a good thing, do you think, for her?", "question_tokens": ["And", "from", "a", "therapeutic", "point", "of", "view", ",", "Sanjay", ",", "would", "something", "like", "today", "with", "the", "outpouring", "of", "emotion", "and", "everything", "else", ",", "would", "that", "be", "seen", "as", "a", "good", "thing", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "for", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "MD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "RB", ",", "MD", "IN", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Well, I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sanjay"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "So I can only assume that you would have been quite happy for your country to go into catastrophic default?", "question_tokens": ["So", "I", "can", "only", "assume", "that", "you", "would", "have", "been", "quite", "happy", "for", "your", "country", "to", "go", "into", "catastrophic", "default", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "Well, then you would have assumed wrong obviously.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "then", "you", "would", "have", "assumed", "wrong", "obviously", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "And finally, Congressman, presumably, you believe that Speaker Boehner should now resign given he's authorized this terrible deal?", "question_tokens": ["And", "finally", ",", "Congressman", ",", "presumably", ",", "you", "believe", "that", "Speaker", "Boehner", "should", "now", "resign", "given", "he", "'s", "authorized", "this", "terrible", "deal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "Of course, I don't believe that.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "believe", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Boehner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "If he's done such a great job, why did you stab him in the back?", "question_tokens": ["If", "he", "'s", "done", "such", "a", "great", "job", ",", "why", "did", "you", "stab", "him", "in", "the", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "I didn't stab him in the back.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "stab", "him", "in", "the", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "Why is that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "For saying things like that, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "saying", "things", "like", "that", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Arianna, why do you say that?", "question_tokens": ["Arianna", ",", "why", "do", "you", "say", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "I say that, Piers, because here we have a major crisis in the country.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "say", "that", ",", "Piers", ",", "because", "here", "we", "have", "a", "major", "crisis", "in", "the", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "Did Nancy Pelosi say that, too?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "Nancy", "Pelosi", "say", "that", ",", "too", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "Apparently, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Apparently", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nancy Pelosi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party"]}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "So the Tea Party, really, have been calling the shots with both sides?", "question_tokens": ["So", "the", "Tea", "Party", ",", "really", ",", "have", "been", "calling", "the", "shots", "with", "both", "sides", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Well, the Tea Party was allowed to call the shots.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "Tea", "Party", "was", "allowed", "to", "call", "the", "shots", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "What do you think today's deal, and the Senate presumably approving it tomorrow, will actually do for parents and families in America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "today", "'s", "deal", ",", "and", "the", "Senate", "presumably", "approving", "it", "tomorrow", ",", "will", "actually", "do", "for", "parents", "and", "families", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Well, that is really the problem, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "is", "really", "the", "problem", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "Do you fear that America, despite all of the protestations to the contrary, that America could go through the same thing that Greece has been through?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "fear", "that", "America", ",", "despite", "all", "of", "the", "protestations", "to", "the", "contrary", ",", "that", "America", "could", "go", "through", "the", "same", "thing", "that", "Greece", "has", "been", "through", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "Well, I'm ultimately an optimist.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "ultimately", "an", "optimist", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "America", "Greece"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "What was your view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Well, I believe that there should have been tax increases, if only for a political matter, because everybody in the country, it seems to me, has to be seen to be participating in what I call shared sacrifice.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "believe", "that", "there", "should", "have", "been", "tax", "increases", ",", "if", "only", "for", "a", "political", "matter", ",", "because", "everybody", "in", "the", "country", ",", "it", "seems", "to", "me", ",", "has", "to", "be", "seen", "to", "be", "participating", "in", "what", "I", "call", "shared", "sacrifice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Here's the question for you, if I get you back on the show in a month's time, are you absolutely certain this no taxation at any cost policy of yours will mean that the economy will have recovered?", "question_tokens": ["Here", "'s", "the", "question", "for", "you", ",", "if", "I", "get", "you", "back", "on", "the", "show", "in", "a", "month", "'s", "time", ",", "are", "you", "absolutely", "certain", "this", "no", "taxation", "at", "any", "cost", "policy", "of", "yours", "will", "mean", "that", "the", "economy", "will", "have", "recovered", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Well, it moves us at least in the right direction.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "moves", "us", "at", "least", "in", "the", "right", "direction", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "At what point do you and the Republicans that agree with your position on taxation stop and think actually we have to consider it?", "question_tokens": ["At", "what", "point", "do", "you", "and", "the", "Republicans", "that", "agree", "with", "your", "position", "on", "taxation", "stop", "and", "think", "actually", "we", "have", "to", "consider", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NNPS", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "I don't think that putting leaches on a patient is ever a good idea.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "putting", "leaches", "on", "a", "patient", "is", "ever", "a", "good", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "What should they be doing with their money right now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "they", "be", "doing", "with", "their", "money", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Well, that's the funny thing about it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "funny", "thing", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]